[
  {
    "id": 132,
    "question": "Which of the following is characteristic of Parkinson's Disease?",
    "options": {
      "a": "fine tremors and rigidity",
      "b": "fine tremors and flaccidity",
      "c": "coarse tremors and rigidity",
      "d": "coarse tremors and flaccidity tremors and rigidity"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "question": "Which disease is due to a significant loss of neurotransmitter in the brain?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Parkinson's disease",
      "b": "muscular distrophy"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "question": "Which structure passes through the intervertebral foramina of the thoracic vertebrae?",
    "options": {
      "a": "vertebral arteries",
      "b": "spinal nerves",
      "c": "spinal cord"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "question": "How many pairs of spinal nerves do we have?",
    "options": {
      "a": "12",
      "b": "24",
      "c": "31",
      "d": "62"
    },
    "correct_option": "c",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "question": "Which of these is a proximal carpal?",
    "options": {
      "a": "lunate",
      "b": "hamate",
      "c": "trapezoid",
      "d": "capitate"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "question": "What is the shaft of a long bone called?",
    "options": {
      "a": "epiphesis",
      "b": "diaphesis",
      "c": "medullary cavity"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "question": "Which kind of bones are the phalanges of the feet?",
    "options": {
      "a": "long bones",
      "b": "short bones",
      "c": "sesamoid",
      "d": "cuboid"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "question": "Which articulates with the occipital condyles?",
    "options": {
      "a": "axis",
      "b": "occipital protuberance",
      "c": "mastoid",
      "d": "atlas"
    },
    "correct_option": "d",
    "correct_answer_text": "atlas"
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "question": "What is the action of Latissimus Dorsi?",
    "options": {
      "a": "lateral rotation of the shoulder",
      "b": "flexion of the shoulder",
      "c": "extension of the neck",
      "d": "depression of the shoulder girdle depression of the shoulder girdle"
    },
    "correct_option": "d",
    "correct_answer_text": "depression of the shoulder girdle"
  },
  {
    "id": 141,
    "question": "Which of these muscles are least involved in respiration?",
    "options": {
      "a": "pelvic floor muscles",
      "b": "deltoids",
      "c": "intercostals",
      "d": "abdominals"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  }
]